{
    "id": "262c5a9cae4a4a92bdaeb1754bd2c21d",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He made a handsome donation ............................. the flood relief fund.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c47175a846d1437d9044d96665a3b854"
        },
        {
            "question": "He quarreled with me .................................... a trivial issue.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "on",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a36a95c3fcd944dd938edbacb4f0bbcf"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not satisfied ................................... your explanation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "with",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "da730f91d1044669ba40093d11960748"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must not be envious ................................... your neighborâ€™s success.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "off",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "232344a1a06c4baa8b92a9f5b997c174"
        },
        {
            "question": "We can only rely ............................... our own efforts.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "over",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c6a794e0426942f7a00d9c62a4e8f56b"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must be prompt ................................. carrying out orders.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d1a241e0738b445e997cd9c82e33a34c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Recently there has been a sharp rise .................................... the price of gold.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "98d009edf15d47e9bf32b91c48872edd"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was born ....................................... poor parents.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f807faeb74124e0abc5e0965bf2b295d"
        },
        {
            "question": "His views do not accord .................................. mine.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "573a00439a52448288fe10b0f2270de5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Temperance and employment are conducive ........................................ health.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c91dc617946a4a7685a38c45d678ea18"
        }
    ]
}